Guide to The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1950-2019 (bulk, 1974-2018) MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Board of Trustees records, 1975-2010; 37 Linear feet in 37 record cartons
  - Subseries II.B. Executive Committee records, 1989-2008; 8 Linear feet in 8 record cartons
    - Agenda and materials, 2005 November-December (Offsite-box 45, Folder 20)
    - Meeting minutes, 2006 January-December (Offsite-box 45, Folder 21)
    - Agenda and materials [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 2006 February-August (Offsite-box 45, Folder 22-24)
    - Agenda and materials [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 2006 September-December (Offsite-box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Meeting transcript (1 of 2), 2006 December 8 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 4)
      Includes letter and 4 CDs from Teleconferencing Services, LLC.
    - Meeting transcript (2 of 2). Digital files, 2006 December 8 (Digital folder MS3199, Folder Box46_F4)
      Contains digital files originally stored on four CDs in Box 46 Folder 4. The files are four WAV audio files containing WSF meeting recording from teleconference service.
    - Agenda and materials [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2007 January-May (Offsite-box 46, Folder 5-6)
    - Agenda and materials [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2007 June-December (Offsite-box 46, Folder 7-8)
    - Agenda and materials [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 January-November (Offsite-box 46, Folder 9-10)
  - Subseries II.C. Advisory Board and Committee records, 1976-2005; 10 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
    The Advisory Board was formed early in the operations of the WSF by first Executive Director Eva Auchincloss with the purpose of setting the direction and priorities for the Foundation. This Advisory Board was composed of champion female athletes acting as representatives of their sports, referred to as "Representative Athletes," as well as representatives from sports-related fields, sport organizations, and corporate supporters. Representatives from sports-related fields included sportswriters, sportscasters, coaches, and publishers. As of 1997, the Advisory Board is described in WSF reports as "the primary collaboration resource of the Foundation," with more than 350 organizations serving and contributing to Foundation projects.
    The Committees are composed of a balance of Trustees, Advisory Board members, and WSF officers and staff. Responsibilities of the Nominating Committee include: identifying, screening, and recommending prospective Trustees, Advisory Board, and officer candidates, assisting in the recruitment and orientation of Trustees, and recommending members of Standing Committees to the Board. Responsibilities of the Finance Committee include: preparing the annual budget and recommending budget adjustments, presenting budget reports to the Board, and recommending financial policies and procedures. Responsibilities of the Awards Committee include designing and implementing procedures for the nomination of and procedures for all WSF awards.
    Subseries II.C contains records of the Advisory Board and of various Committees, including the Nominating Committee, Finance Committee, Awards Committee, and Strategic Planning Committee. Records include meeting agendas and minutes, correspondence, and reports and document Advisory Board and Committee operations and activity and communication with the WSF Executive Directors and Board of Trustees. Records date from 1976-2005.
    - Advisory Board minutes, 1976-1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 11)
    - Advisory Board updates, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 12)
    - Eva Auchincloss correspondence, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 13)
    - Proposal copies, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 14)
    - New Agenda proposal, 1983 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 15)
    - USAmateur Athletic Travel Union, 1983 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 16)
    - Nominating Committee recommendations, 1994 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 8)
    - Policies, 1984 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 17)
    - Sports record book, 1984 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 18)
    - Summary, 1984 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 19)
    - Nominating Committee, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 20)
    - Board member signature, circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 21)
    - Current proposals, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 22)
    - New Agenda regional conferences, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 23)
    - Voting membership, circa 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 24)
    - Former Advisory Board organizations, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 25)
    - Advisory Board and committee documents, 1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 26)
    - Advisory Board updates, 1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 29)
    - Finance committee, 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 1)
    - LPGA correspondence, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 2)
    - Board meeting, 1986 May 19 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 3)
    - Eva Auchincloss correspondence, 1987 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 5)
    - Inventory, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 6)
    - Speakers Bureau income, circa 1987 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 7)
    - Tax returns, 1987 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 8)
    - National Federation of State High School Associations, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 9)
    - 800 number research, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 10)
    - Aspire Higher letters to organizations, 1988 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 11)
    - Insurance professional compensation planners, 1988 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 12)
    - Office policies, 1988 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 13)
    - Nomination committee, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 14)
    - Awards committee, 1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 15)
    - Meetings and reports, 1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 16)
    - WATTS line project itemized by area code, 1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 17)
    - WSF background information, circa 1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 18)
    - Executive committee, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 19)
    - Oakland A's, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 20)
    - Advisory Board, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee reports, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 22)
    - Trustee and Advisory Board responsibilities, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 23)
    - Handbook, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 24)
    - Hazelden-Cork sports education, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 25)
    - Management committee, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 26)
    - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 27)
    - Policies/ procedures handbook, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 28)
    - Salute to Women in Sports, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 29)
    - Succession planning committee, 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 30)
    - Advisory Board dues, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 31)
    - Membership information, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 32)
    - Advisory Board mailing, 1991 March 22 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 33)
    - Strategic plan, 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 34)
    - Negative replies Advisory Board, 1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 35)
    - Advisory Board mailing, 1992 July 21 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 36)
    - Strategic planning committee, 1992 August (Offsite-box 47, Folder 37)
    - Advisory Board members' cars, 1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 38)
    - Lease 230 Park Avenue Helmsley-Spear, Inc., 1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 39)
    - Nominating committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 40)
    - Nominating Committee [disassembled binder], 1992-1998 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 41)
    - Strategic Planning committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 1)
    - Structure and function committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 2)
    - All councils, 1992 July 17 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 3)
    - Advisory Board mailing, 1992 July 21 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Board mailing, 1992 August 20 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 5)
    - Nominating committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 6)
    - Strategic plan, 1994 January 5 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 7)
    - Ad hoc committee on logo/ branding conference call, 1998 March 19 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 8)
    - Ad hoc committee on the Amateur Sport Act, 1998 August 27 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 9)
    - Strategic planning committee meeting, 2001 April 11 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 10)
    - Governance nominating committee (6 folders), 2002-2005 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 11-16)
    - Strategic planning (2 folders), 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 195, Folder 19-20)
    - Memberships NCAA affiliation, 1998 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 10)
    - Advisory Board mailing, 1993 June 9 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 11)
    - Board of Stewards, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 12)
    - Board of Stewards response letter, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 13)
    - Advocacy committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 14)
    - Audit committee, 2004 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 15)
    - Finance committee (2 folders), 1987-1999 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 57-58)
    - Finance committee correspondence, 1999 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 59)
    - Committee on ethical relationships between sports leaders and athletes, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 60)
    - Hall of Fame design committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 61)
    - Properties committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 62)
    - Amateur Sports Act committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 63)
    - Awards committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 64)
    - Research network, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 65)
    - International committee (Offsite-box 206, Folder 66)
    - LPGA steering committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 67)
    - Membership committee, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 68)
    - Site selection committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 69)
    - Gender equity task force NCAA, 1993 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 70)
    - Committee on concerns of women of diverse races, 1992 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 72)
    - Strategic planning (2 folders), 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 207, Folder 1-2)
    - Structure and functions committee (2 folders), 1997-2000 (Offsite-box 207, Folder 3-4)
    - Structure and functions committee (2 folders), 1993-1997 (Offsite-box 207, Folder 5-6)
    - Drug policy committee (2 folders), 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 207, Folder 7-8)
    - Steering and Training committee (1 of 5 boxes), 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 221)
      Contains strategic plan, to-do list, contact lists for steering and training committee, steering committee organizational information, early EHIS project information, and project director playbook.
    - Steering and Training committee (2 of 5 boxes), 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 222)
      Contains Trainers Network Contact information, Teaching Tolerance, Richardson Foundation, Media Education Foundation, IBM Negotiations, Team IBM, contact Information.
    - Steering and Training committee (3 of 5 boxes), 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 223)
      Contains Strategic Action Plan Organization Files, Organizations already targeted and approached, prior presentation files.
    - Steering and Training committee (4 of 5 boxes), 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 224)
      Contains Strategic Action Plan Organization Files, organizations already targeted and approached, prior presentation files, and materials from NGLA Conferences 2003-2004 including binders and correspondence.
    - Steering and Training committee (5 of 5 boxes), 2002-2004 (Offsite-box 225)
      Contains fundraising, outreach, public relations records.
    - Staff planning, annual planning, and strategic planning, 1994-1998 (Offsite-box 226)
  - Subseries II.D. Trustees biographical files, 1975-2010; 6 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    Subseries II.D contains Trustee biographical files originally stored in WSF office filing cabinets. Trustee files contain a range of documentation of each Trustee, including press and article clippings, correspondence with WSF staff, and reports of Trustee activities with WSF. Documents date from 1975-2010.
    Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - A (7 folders), 1988-2009 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 17-23)
    - B (6 folders), 1990-2007 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 24-29)
    - C (4 folders), 1998-2008 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 30-33)
    - D (2 of 10 folders), 1998-2008 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 34-35)
    - D (8 of 10 folders), 1982-2008 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 1-8)
    - E (6 folders), 1982-2006 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 9-14)
    - F (10 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 15-24)
    - G (2 of 10 folders), 1990-2008 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 25-26)
    - G (8 of 10 folders), 1990-2008 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 1-8)
    - H (10 folders), 1984-2008 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 9-18)
    - J (4 folders), 1989-2004 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 19-22)
    - Ka-Ke (5 folders), 1977-2007 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 23-27)
    - King, Billie Jean (1 of 8 folders), 1975-2010 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 28)
    - King, Billie Jean (7 of 8 folders), 1975-2010 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 1-7)
    - Ki-Ko (7 folders), 1987-2010 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 8-14)
    - La-Li (9 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 15-23)
    - Lopiano, Donna (3 of 7 folders), 1987-2007 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 24-26)
    - Lopiano, Donna (4 of 7 folders), 1987-2007 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 1-4)
    - Lo, 2002-2008 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 5)
    - M (14 folders), 1979-2008 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 6-19)
    - N (4 folders), 1985-2007 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 20-23)
    - O (3 folders), 1986-2007 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 24-26)
    - P, 1990-2003 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 27)
    - R (2 of 7 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 52, Folder 28-29)
    - R (5 of 7 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 1-5)
    - Sa-St (18 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 53, Folder 6-23)
    - Sw-Sy (2 folders), 1987-2008 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - T (3 folders), 1990-2008 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 3-5)
    - V (6 folders), 1986-2008 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 6-11)
    - Wa-We (4 folders), 1992-2007 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 12-15)
    - New Trustees photos, 1998 (Offsite-box 54, Folder 16)
    - Trustees and advisory board nomination and subject files Wa-Z (41 folders), 1992-2007 (Offsite-box 206, Folder 16-56)
- Series III. Staff records, 1974-2014; 30 Linear feet in 30 record cartons
  Series III contains WSF staff records from various individuals and offices, including Executive Directors Eva Auchincloss, Deborah Slaner Anderson, and Donna Lopiano, as well as Dr. Marjorie Snyder and from the Chief Financial Officer office. Records include correspondence, reports, research and subject files, meeting notes and minutes, and publications. The records document the leadership, operations, finances, programming, and publications of the WSF. Records date from 1974-2014.
  Arranged in five subseries:
  Subseries III.A. Executive Director Eva Auchincloss records
  Subseries III.B. Executive Director Deborah Slaner Anderson records
  Subseries III.C. Executive Director Donna Lopiano records
  Subseries III.D. Marjorie Snyder records
  Subseries III.E. Chief Financial Officer records
  - Subseries III.A. Executive Director Eva Auchincloss records, 1983-1986; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Eva Auchincloss was the founding Executive Director of the WSF and was responsible for implementing most of the fundraising and educational programs of the Foundation. Before her appointment as Executive Director in January 1976, she served as the Associate Publisher of womenSports magazine from 1974. Upon appointment, Auchincloss recruited the Advisory Board of the WSF, composed of athlete representatives and representatives from a variety of sports-related fields. Achievements during her tenure included: establishing the New York Awards Dinner as a fundraising event and showcase, spearheading and planning The New Agenda conference held in 1983, and implementing educational programs, particularly the toll-free information and referral line, publication of camp scholarship and athletic scholarship guides, and the High School All-Star awards program. Her term as Executive Director ended in 1986.
    Subseries III.A contains records of Eva Auchincloss, the first Executive Director of the WSF, who served as Executive Director from 1976-1986. Records include documents describing WSF history, research files, correspondence, Board meeting minutes and reports, publications, and subject files. Records date from 1983-1986.
    - Eva's files: WSF history (2 folders), 1983-2002 (Offsite-box 59, Folder 28-29)
    - The New Agenda (5 folders), 1983 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 9-13)
    - St. Francis college, 1983 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 14)
    - Biathlon problem, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 15)
    - Board of Trustees and Advisory Board materials, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 16)
    - College scholarship guide controversy (2 folders), 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 17-18)
    - Equal Pay magazine copies, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 19)
    - Equal rights/ legal issues, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 20)
    - Health/ sports medicine issues, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 21)
    - Publicity for the N.A. regional conferences, 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 22)
    - [United States Collegiate Sports Council], 1985 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 23)
    - Lynn Mueller [correspondence], 1985 (Offsite-box 267, Folder 2)
    - NCAA problem, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 24)
    - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists dispute, 1986 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 25)
    - College cutbacks, 1986 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 26)
    - Education/ issue, 1986 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 27)
    - Board meeting Innisbrook, 1986 February (Offsite-box 55, Folder 28)
    - Coaches Roundtable and Advisory Council minutes, 1986 (Offsite-box 267, Folder 3)
  - Subseries III.B. Executive Director Deborah Slaner Anderson records, 1985-1992; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Deborah Slaner Anderson was the WSF Executive Director from 1986-1991. Anderson took over the direction of the Foundation upon the move from San Francisco to New York. During her tenure, the Foundation successfully raised $3 million through the two-year "Aspire Higher" fundraising campaign. Anderson doubled the revenues from the annual awards dinner and quadrupled the endowment fund.
    Subseries III.B contains records of Deborah Slaner Anderson, WSF Executive Director from 1986-1991. Records include correspondence, reports, marketing materials, memos, and a series of files labelled as the "Chronological files" that include correspondence with Trustees, advisors, and donors. Of particular interest are an organizational chart and programs list for the WSF from 1988 and long-range planning documentation from 1989. Records date from 1985-1992.
    - Correspondence, reports, and notes (1 of 7 folders), 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 55, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, reports, and notes (6 of 7 folders), 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 7-9)
    - Aspire Higher marketing campaign (3 folders), 1987 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 10-12)
    - Board membership letters, 1987 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 13)
    - Strategic plan presentation (3 folders), 1987 March 19 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 14-16)
    - Correspondence, 1987 August-1988 February (Offsite-box 56, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 18)
    - Organizational chart and programs list, 1988 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 19)
    - President's Commission, 1988 (Offsite-box 56, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1988 February-June (Offsite-box 57, Folder 1)
    - Donor mailing, 1988 December (Offsite-box 57, Folder 2)
    - Business plan for 1989 and long range goals for 1993, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 3)
    - WSF drug policy committee conference call, 1989 June 26 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 4)
    - Chronological file (22 folders), 1990 July-1992 March (Offsite-box 57, Folder 5-26)
      Contains a range of folders labelled as the "Chronological files," which include correspondence with Trustees, advisors, and donors from Deborah Slaner Anderson and Executive Assistants. Files are organized by month.
    - Dot Harris memo, 1990 November (Offsite-box 57, Folder 27)
    - Burroughs Wellcome Company proposal, 1991 July (Offsite-box 57, Folder 28)
  - Subseries III.C. Executive Director Donna Lopiano, 1992-2007; 2.5 Linear feet in 2.5 record cartons
    Deborah Lopiano was the WSF Executive Director from 1992-2002 and the Chief Executive Officer from 2002 until her resignation in 2007. Prior to coming to the WSF, Lopiano was the Athletic Director of Women Athletics at the University of Texas. At the WSF, Lopiano developed the Community Awards and Grants program, secured funds that enabled the WSF to award more than $14 million in cash grants and free education curricula, and expanded the WSF endowment to $4 million.
    Subseries III.C contains records of Donna Lopiano, Executive Director from 1992-2002 and Chief Executive Officer from 2002-2007. Records include correspondence with Trustees, advisors, and donors from Lopiano, minutes and reports from the Board of Trustees, Advisory Board, Executive Committees, and various Ad Hoc Committees, and speeches. Records date 1992-2007.
    Records are arranged as received from the donor.
    - Chronological file, 1992 April (Offsite-box 57, Folder 29)
    - Chronological file (10 folders), 1992 May-December (Offsite-box 58, Folder 1-10)
      Contains a range of folders labelled as the "Chronological files," which include correspondence with Trustees, advisors, and donors from Donna Lopiano. Files are organized by month.
    - Executive Committee and ad hoc committees, 1997 (Offsite-box 106, Folder 20)
    - Ad hoc committees, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Board playbook [disassembled binder], 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees meeting agenda and materials, 1995 February 1 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 3)
    - Annual corporate partner's meeting materials, 1996 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 4)
    - Congressional hearings, 1995 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 5)
    - Women's United Soccer Association planning (8 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 107, Folder 6-13)
    - Correspondence chronological file (2 of 34 folders), 2005 March (Offsite-box 107, Folder 16-17)
    - Chronological correspondence file (32 of 34 folders), 2005 May-2007 October (Offsite-box 108, Folder 1-32)
    - Speeches and writings (9 folders), 1987-1995 (Offsite-box 116, Folder 7-15)
  - Subseries III.D. Marjorie Snyder records, 1988-2007; 11.5 Linear feet in 11.5 record cartons
    Dr. Marjorie Snyder had previously held various positions at the WSF, including Chief Program & Planning Officer, Senior Director of Research & Programs, and Interim co-CEO on two occasions. While serving the WSF, Dr. Snyder directed the advocacy, education, research and planning efforts of the Foundation, co-authored research reports, developed the GoGirlGo! Project, and served as Foundation spokesperson and speaker at national and international conferences. Dr. Snyder is also largely credited with collecting and maintaining the archival records of the WSF within their offices. As of 2021, Dr. Snyder is the Senior Research Advisor at the WSF.
    Subseries III.D contains records of Dr. Marjorie Snyder, who has worked for and with the WSF in various capacities from 1987. Records include correspondence, publicity and marketing materials, PSAs (public service announcements), program proposals and files, calendars, publications, event programs, and a file of WSF publications, including scholarship guides, research reports, and educational pamphlets. Records date from 1988-2007.
    - WSF history, 1999-2003 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 11)
    - C'mon mom PSA, 2000 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 12)
    - PSAs memos and correspondence, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 13)
    - PSA Ideas - Jordan McGrath Case & Taylor, 2000 August (Offsite-box 58, Folder 14)
    - BJK 60th/30th Anniversary Riggs Match - PSA, 2003 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 15)